https://www.nist.ac.th/privacy-policy-disclosure/

Privacy Policy Disclosure
NIST International School (hereafter referred to as NIST or the School) strongly believes in safeguarding the wellbeing of its community. To that end, our school invests significant resources in protecting the privacy of our staff, parents and children. In order to ensure that we achieve this aim, we have adopted the following policy in line with international privacy standards.
Definitions
Staff are individuals employed by NIST in any capacity, including full-time and part-time employees. This excludes contracted companies and individuals.
Students are current, prospective or past students enrolled at NIST.
Parents are current, prospective or past parents, and/or legal guardians, of a student or students at NIST.
Alumni are former NIST students and/or graduates.
Where applicable in the policy, alumni will be differentiated between those over the age of 18 and those under the age of 18.
Third parties are individuals or organizations that are not affiliated with or employed by NIST.
Personal information constitutes the full legal name, personal address, personal contact information and school records of an individual. It does not include identification numbers, names of staff, or titles and business contact information of staff.
Policies
NIST will make these policies publicly accessible, and will make every reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information is accurate and protected. This includes the storing of all personal information only in password-protected databases.
Personal information of students, parents and staff of NIST is stored within Veracross. Veracross LLC maintains a privacy policy that has been certified by TRUSTe Privacy Standards and can be accessed at veracross.com/privacy-policy.
Personal information of alumni is stored within 360Alumni. 360Alumni maintains a privacy policy that can be accessed at 360alumni.com/privacy-policy.
All staff, parents, students and alumni agree upon initiating their relationship with NIST that the School shall keep their personal information on file in Veracross for the duration of their time as members of the School community as a matter of academic record, evidence of services rendered and/or as evidence of employment.
NIST may publicly disclose non-personal information of staff, including titles, business addresses, and business contact information. Personal information will be disclosed to third parties only with the consent of that member of staff.
In line with the US Department of Education’s Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), NIST will not disclose the personal information of a student to third parties without the consent of the student’s parent. Personal information of an alumnus or alumna will not disclose the personal information to third parties without the consent of that alumnus or alumna. This excludes non-identifiable disclosure of academic records for the purposes of accreditation, academic research, statistical analysis, and disclosure under subpoena by Thai law.
As indicated in the NIST enrollment documents, NIST reserves the right to use photographs and other visual media containing the images of NIST parents, students and alumni in online and print media. In such cases the school will not post the full legal names of students or alumni who have yet to reach the age of 18 with that media, unless permission is granted from parents, to preserve their privacy.
Instances of online media include, but are not limited to, the NIST website, social media channels such as Facebook, news sites that publish NIST press releases, and third parties which have been granted permission by NIST for the purposes of promotion of education-related content.
Instances of print media include, but are not limited to, school brochures and flyers, the school magazine, advertisements, newspapers and magazines that publish NIST press releases, and third parties which have been granted permission by NIST for the purposes of promotion of education-related content.
In cases in which published media, whether in online or print form, utilizes extensive interviews with students, further consent will be sought from the parents of those students.
As a not-for-profit school that provides educational services within the Kingdom of Thailand, to a degree NIST falls outside the scope of the the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). However, the School abides by the GDPR in respect to the processing of personal information of European Union residents who repatriate and/or offer donations to NIST:
The personal information of all European Union residents who repatriate following enrollment or employment at NIST will be stored in Veracross as per the agreement signed during the enrollment and re-enrollment processes, and/or the employment contract. Should any individual wish to exercise the right to be forgotten, their account in Veracross shall be stripped of identifiable information. The identification number, role classification and, if applicable, academic records shall remain on file.
All European Union residents who are donors to NIST will be asked to give special consent when receiving or storing their personal information for any purpose, including, but not limited to, record keeping, publication or other purposes appropriate to the School’s operations.
Cookies & Tracking
NIST utilizes Google Analytics in tracking visitors to the NIST website. This information is not used to identify personal information, nor is it used for any purpose other than improvement of the website based on identifiable trends. Cookies – small pieces of information stored on your computer to indicate sites that you have visited – are used only in conjunction with Google Analytics for the purpose of enhancing the NIST website. These cookies are not used to gather personal information about visitors, and no other visitor tracking is conducted. Additional information about Google Analytics and privacy is available on the Google Support website.
Additional Resources
These resources provide additional information and guidance in the issues surrounding student privacy. Please note that they are not unequivocally endorsed by NIST or its staff.
Electronic Privacy Information Center (EPIC)
The Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA)
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Student Privacy Initiative
Student Privacy Matters
×
Mr. Sarath Ratanavadi
Chairman
Education
Bachelor’s Degree in Engineering, Chulalongkorn University
M.Sc. in Civil Engineering, University of Southern California, U.S.A.
Occupation
Chief Executive Officer of Gulf Energy Development PCL
×
Mr. Ravi Sawhney
Founding Member
Education
B.A. (Honours) Economics
Bachelor of Law
Occupation
As member of the Indian Administrative Service (IAS), served in several important positions in the state and central governments in India for about 20 years
Worked in the United Nations Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific (ESCAP) for about 18 years and retired as Principal Officer in 2006
International consultant in the field of international trade and investment and on the board of several companies in India
While in ESCAP,spear-headed the initiative to establish a UN school in Bangkok which eventually led to the establishment of NIST in 1992. Since then, has been intimately involved in the development of NIST, as a Trustee in the Foundation. Also served as Chairman of the Foundation during the formative years of the School
In view of his role in the establishment of NIST,has been appointed for life as Founding Member of the Foundation
×
Mr. Bruce G. Hemmingsen
Secretary
Education
Diploma in Management, New Zealand Institute of Management (NZIM)
Post Graduate Diploma in Management, SLOAN-MIT
Occupation
Senior Vice President – IDS Medical Systems (Thailand) Co., Ltd.
Children at NIST: 1 (Class of 2023)
×
Ms. Pornpan Chayasuntorn
Member
Education
LL.M., University of Pennsylvania Law School, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, U.S.A.
M.CL., Indiana University School of Law, Bloomington, Indiana, U.S.A.
LL.B., Thammasat University
Occupation
Lawyer, Linklaters (Thailand) Ltd.
Children at NIST: 1 (Class of 2025)
×
Mr. Prabsharan Singh Thakral
School Board Chair
Education
Kellogg-HKUST Executive M.BA.
M.Sc. Business Systems Analysis and Design , City University, London
B.Sc. Business Management, King’s College, London
Occupation
Group CEO, Boutique Asset Management Ltd.
Children at NIST: 3 (Class of 2023, 2028 & 2031)
×
Mr. Tanon Tantisunthorn
Member
Education
M.BA. American University
Master of Science, New York University
Bachelor of Engineering, Chulalongkorn University
Occupation
Vice President, Gulf Energy Development Co., Ltd.
Children at NIST: 2 (Class of 2029 & 2033)
×
Mr. William Angus Kent
Treasurer
Education
M.Sc., International Economics and Finance, University of Queensland
Chartered Financial Analyst designation
Occupation
Managing Director, Macquarie Securities Thailand
Children at NIST: 2 (Class of 2021 & 2023)
×
Ms. Angkana Uthaisangchai
Member
Education
Master in Design Studies, Harvard University, Graduate School of Design
Bachelor in Architecture (Honors), Chulalongkorn University, Faculty of Architecture
Occupation
Architectural Design Director, Thanaland Co. Ltd.
Children at NIST: 3 (Class of 2029 & 2031)
×
Ms. Narawadee Bualert
Member
Education
M.B.A., Sasin Graduate Institute of Business Administration of Chulalongkorn University, Thailand
B.Sc. in Management, Royal Holloway University of London, UK
Occupation
President of Lebua Hotels & Resorts
Children at NIST: 2 (Class of 2027 & 2029)
×
Dr. Nattavut Kulnides
Member
Education
Bachelor of Science, Mitibai College, Chauhan Institute of Science, Mumbai, India
Occupation
Housewife
Children at NIST: 1 (Class of 2023)
Welcome to NIST!
“The community understands and has embraced the shift from an achievement-oriented to a growth-oriented learning model and its connection to developing lifelong learners.”— 2018 NEASC Accreditation Report
Welcome to NIST International School
The first and only full, not-for-profit International Baccalaureate (IB) international school in Bangkok, Thailand
Our History
Our Mission, Vision & Values
Our Strategic Plan
Our Leadership
Our Governance
Our Campus & Facilities
×
Book a School Tour
We encourage all families to make an appointment to tour the school. Your visit will offer you a unique view into our community and allow us to provide more in-depth information in order to help you make the best educational decision for your family.
Admissions
First and foremost, thank you for considering NIST as an option for your child. As you explore our site and admissions information, we encourage you to contact us with any questions or concerns you may have about our curriculum, philosophy or any other aspect of the school.
Tuition & Fees
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Procedures
Touring the School | Age/Year Level Equivalents
Family Support
Moving to Bangkok | Starting at NIST | Leaving NIST & Bangkok
×
The IB Programme
The International Baccalaureate (IB) does not merely promote a curriculum, but rather a mission to transform the world through education.
Academics
Our community has cultivated a well-deserved reputation for excellence in academics over the past two decades. Being the first full International Baccalaureate (IB) World School in Thailand and a frequent early adopter of programme developments, NIST enjoys an unparalleled relationship with the IB, remaining at the forefront of progressive, research-based teaching and learning.
The IB
Primary Years Programme | Middle Years Programme | Diploma Programme | CAS | Subjects | World Languages
Student Support
Counseling | English as an Additional Language (EAL)
School Performance
Technology & Learning
Global Citizen Diploma
Experiential Education
×
Positive Impact
“We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an act, but a habit.”– William Durant –
Extra Curricular Activities
NIST encourages all students to push beyond their limits through the Extra-Curricular Activities (ECAs) Programme, which offers more than 300 activities in areas as diverse as sports, drama, music, art, technology, academics, language, and social and environmental activism.
NIST Music Academy
Service & Activism
Sports
Chelsea FC International Development Centre Bangkok
×
We believe in the power of education
All of the members of the NIST community, past and present, see education as a force that can enlighten and transform.
Welcome to NIST International School
The first and only full, not-for-profit International Baccalaureate (IB) international school in Bangkok, Thailand
NIPTA
Cultural Groups
Safety & Security
Air Quality
NIST Libraries
Transportation
NIST Catering
Giving at NIST
×
Get in touch
We welcome your inquiry, and would be happy to respond to any queries you may have for you and your family.
Contact Us
Directions & Contact Information
Campus Map
Employment
×
Main Page
Our History
Our Mission, Vision & Values
Tuition & Fees
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
Procedures
Touring the School
Age/Year Level Equivalents
Family Support
Moving to Bangkok
Starting at NIST
Leaving NIST & Bangkok
×
Counseling
English as an Additional Language (EAL)
Global Citizen Diploma
Experiential Education
Technology & Learning
×
Main Page
NIST Music Academy
Service & Activism
Sports
×
We may use "cookies" to enhance the user experience of our website. By continuing to use our website, we note that you accept the use of cookies for this purpose.I AcceptPrivacy Policy
